Address: 1 Balcurris Gardens, Ballymun D11C971

Phone: +353 85 760 6691 Email: rabunje@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

A self-motivated, goal oriented professional with several years of experience in the areas of reception, administration, Sales, Customer Retention, Operations, Leadership and Management. An effective communicator who is proficient at creating and executing Strategic plans. Possesses excellent Leadership, Customer Success & Innovation skills while remaining calm under pressure. Has a positive and proactive approach to solving problems and achieving goals as well as making sure clients receive the best quality service possible for their needs.

WORK HISTORY

Front Desk Receptionist

Crowne Plaza & Holiday Inn Express Hotels Northwood Park, August – Present

- Check-in, respond to requests and settle accounts while providing exceptional service.
- Promote the hotel facilities while looking for opportunities to enhance a guests stay through up-selling.
- Assume the responsibility for the security of the room keys.
- Answer guests queries and handle complaints and escalate sensitive issues.
- Answer phone calls, email management, and correspondence
- Make guest registration and room reservations.
- Verify and imprint credit cards for authorization and verify payments methods.
- Manage conference room bookings and scheduling organizations.

Administrative Assistant, 03/2020 to 01/2022

Consolidated Bank of Kenva

- Responsible for general reception duties, screening of phone calls as required and communicating messages to personnel promptly, accurately and dealing with any queries where possible.
- Ensure all visitors and non-office-based staff are signed in/out.
- Support to office/team administration roles in other Head Office departments.
- Scanning, filing, and photocopying of documents.
- Meeting and greeting visitors and directing them to the appropriate person.
- Manage office supplies and Inventory management.
- Responsible for general office tidiness and upkeep of the reception area.
- Monitoring meeting room bookings.
- Minute taking at meetings and diary management.
- Assistance with the setting up of video conference meetings and telephone conference calls based in the meeting rooms as necessary on Teams as required.
- Responsible for the tidiness of meeting rooms, provision of refreshments for meetings when required and clearing up after meetings in preparation for next use.
- Organize and manage couriers, taxis and printing as required.

- Update and maintain the company SharePoint intranet.
- Guest and client's confidential data protection.
- Preparation and assistance of reports as and when required.
- Open, sort, scan and distribute all incoming post and ensure all outgoing post is sent daily including special deliveries as necessary.
- Setup and management of access pass for staff. (Create access pass for new starters)

Customer Service Representative,

04/2017 to 01/2020

Safaricom PLC - Kenya

- Followed through with leads to close sales over the phone, office, and external consumer engagements (Tele-Sales)
- Improved customer relationships through delivery of consistent customer service.
- Examined needs, wants and spending patterns of target audience by an outstanding customer service in improving customer satisfaction and retention.
- Managed sales promotions and marketing strategies on major social media sites.
- Obtain customer feedback through follow-up calls, both during and after a purchase, calmly and professionally handle customer concerns.
- Provided suggestions and recommendations on process improvement and ways to increase customer satisfaction.
- Researched competitor marketing trends and prices using data analysis.
- Conducted quality assurance surveys with customers and reported findings to the department.
- Performed all other duties assigned.

Intern - Finance Department, 01/2014 to 06/2014

Mumias Sugar Company - Kenya

- Managed client accounts and took necessary actions to receive payments.
- Prepared weekly and monthly reports.
- Management of accounts receivables and accounts payables
- Participated in underwriting procedures for the finance department.
- Assisted in entering transactions on the accounting software.
- Undertaking bank reconciliation,
- Processed staff expenses, paying money into the bank, and dealing with petty cash.
- Maintenance and Updated files and records
- Payroll- Assisted in preparation of monthly wages.
- Routine administrative tasks

Health Advocate, 02/2012 to 04/2012

Kenya Red Cross Society - Kenya

- Took part in the fight against the spread of Jiggers infection in the community.
- Peer education
- Visited less fortunate in the society and donated essential needs.

EDUCATION QUALIFICATIONS

MBA, International Business, 02/2022 to Present

Griffith College - Dublin, Ireland

BBA, Business Management, and Information Technology, 12/2016

Kabarak University - Nakuru, Kenya

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Experience in dealing with customers both by phone and face to face interactions.
- Excellent interpersonal and communication skills
- Passion and commitment to offering a great service experience to customers and promoting the brand.
- Resolve product issues through consumer testing.
- Used Microsoft Excel to develop inventory tracking spreadsheets.
- Achieved targets by completing delegated tasks with accuracy and efficiency.

SKILLS

- Proficient in the use of Microsoft Office Applications (Word, Excel, Access, PowerPoint)
- High level customer Service orientation to see through their resolution.
- Ability to work in a high-paced work environment.
- Knowledge in MS PowerPoint, Excel, Word, and Outlook
- proven ability to work unsupervised as part of a team.
- Experience in invoicing, CRM systems and Opera
- Product management and pricing
- Task prioritization
- Demonstrated ability to deliver quality work in a timely manner.
- proven record of commitment to professional and client service excellence
- Product and service knowledge
- Sales and after sales support
- Approachable and highly professional in manner, with all levels of staff within the organization
- Negotiation and issues resolution skills.
- Excellent communication skills, English & Swahili both written and oral